scrappygeek.com 2017-12-16

# Privacy Policy and Disclosure

**Disclosure**

We are a participant in the Amazon Services LLC Associates Program, an affiliate advertising program designed to provide a means for us to earn fees by linking to Amazon.com and affiliated sites.

This site contains affiliate links and sponsored content.

* * *

This privacy policy discloses the privacy practices for ScrappyGeek.com. This privacy policy applies solely to information collected by this web site, on this website or through third party subscribe forms.

**Information Collection, Use, and Sharing**  
We are the sole owners of the information collected on this site. We only have access to/collect information that you voluntarily give us via email or other direct contact from you. We will not sell or rent this information to anyone.

We will use your information to respond to you, regarding the reason you contacted us. We will not share your information with any third party outside of our organization, other than as necessary to fulfill your request, e.g. to ship an order.

**Your Access to and Control Over Information**  
You may opt out of any future contacts from us at any time. You can do the following at any time by contacting us via the email address or use the unsubscribe link within the email you’ve received.

**Security**  
We take precautions to protect your information. When you submit sensitive information via the website, your information is protected both online and offline.

We take your privacy very seriously and will never share your information with third parties with the exception of what is outlined in this privacy policy.

**Updates**

Our Privacy Policy may change from time to time and all updates will be posted on this page.

If you have any questions, please [contact me](http://scrappygeek.com/contact-me/).
